- [Jay-Z] ♪ It's big pimpin' baby ♪
♪ That's right ♪
♪ Big pimpin', spending cheese ♪
♪ G-g-g--gyeah ♪
♪ You know I thug 'em, hug
'em, love 'em, leave 'em ♪
♪ But I don't trust or need 'em ♪
♪ Take 'em out the hood,
keep 'em looking good ♪
♪ With diamond cuffs then I freeze 'em ♪
♪ First time they fuss I'm breezin' ♪
♪ Talk about what's the reasons ♪
♪ I'm a pimp in every
sense of the word, mama ♪
♪ Better trust and believe 'em ♪
♪ In the cut where I keep 'em ♪
♪ 'Til I need a what, 'til
I need to beat it up ♪
♪ Then it's beep, beep ♪
♪ And I'm pickin' them up ♪
♪ Let 'em play with it
quick in the truck ♪
♪ Many chicks wanna put
Jigga fists in cuffs ♪
♪ Divorce him and split his bucks ♪
♪ Just because you got good sex ♪
♪ I'ma break bread, so
you can be living it up ♪
Hah
♪ I parts with nothing,
y'all be fronting ♪
♪ Me, give my heart to a woman ♪
♪ Not for nothing, never happen ♪
♪ I'll be forever mackin' ♪
♪ Heart cold as assassins,
I got no passion ♪
♪ I got no patience and I hate waiting ♪
♪ Get your (censored) in here
and let's ri-i-i-i-i-ide ♪
♪ Check 'em out now, ri-i-i-i-i-ide ♪
♪ And let's ri-i-i-i-i-ide ♪
♪ We doing big pimpin',
we spending cheese ♪
♪ Check 'em out now, big
pimpin' on B.L.A.D.'s ♪
♪ We doing big pimpin' up in N.Y.C. ♪
♪ It's just that Jigga Man,
Pimp C, and B-you-N B ♪
Yo, yo, yo
♪ Big pimpin', spending cheese ♪
♪ We doing big pimpin' on B.L.A.D.'s ♪
♪ We doing big pimpin' up in N.Y.C. ♪
♪ It's just that Jigga Man,
Pimp C, and B-you-N B ♪
♪ You know I ♪
- [Bun B] ♪ Big southern rap impresario ♪
♪ Coming straight up
out the black barrio ♪
♪ Makes a mil' up off a sorry what ♪
♪ Then sit back and peep my scenario ♪
♪ Oops, my bad, that's my scenario ♪
♪ No, I can't (censored) with scary what ♪
♪ Now every time, every
place, everywhere we go ♪
♪ Start pointing, they say there he go ♪
♪ Now these (censored) know we
carry more than a little bit ♪
♪ We don't pull it out (censored) ♪
♪ And if you catch a lick when I spit ♪
♪ Then it won't be a little hit ♪
♪ Go read a book, you
illiterate son of a (censored) ♪
and step up yo vocab
♪ Don't be surprised (censored) ♪
♪ With me and you see us
coming down on your slab ♪
♪ You look so mad, you
just can't take it ♪
♪ But (censored) if you hatin' ♪
♪ Then you wait while I get
your (censored) butt-naked ♪
♪ Just break it ♪
♪ You gotta pay like you weigh
with two pairs of clothes on ♪
♪ Now get yo' (censored) in the back ♪
♪ As I'm flying to the track ♪
♪ Timbaland let me spit my pros on ♪
♪ Pump it up in the pro-zone ♪
♪ That's the track that we
breakin' these (censored) on ♪
♪ Ain't the track that we flows on ♪
♪ But when (censored) get hot ♪
♪ The (censored) starts
poppin' like the o-zone ♪
♪ We keep (censored)
crunk like (censored) ♪
♪ Fo' real it don't get no bigger man ♪
♪ Don't trip, let's flip,
gettin' trowed on the flip ♪
♪ Gettin' blow with the
(censored) Jigga man, fool ♪
- [Jay-Z] ♪ We be... Big
pimpin', spending cheese ♪
♪ We be... Big pimpin', on B.L.A.D.'s ♪
♪ We be... Big pimpin' down at P.A.T. ♪
♪ It's just that Jigga Man,
Pimp C, and B-you-N B ♪
♪ We be... Big pimpin', spendin' cheese ♪
♪ We be... Big pimpin', on B.L.A.D.'s ♪
♪ We be... Big pimpin', down at P.A.T. ♪
♪ It's just that Jigga Man,
Pimp C, and B-you-N B ♪
- [Pimp C] ♪ Smokin' out, throwin' up, ♪
♪ keepin' lean up in my cup, ♪
♪ All my car got leather and wood, ♪
♪ In my hood we call it buck ♪
♪ Everybody want to ball,
holla at broads in the mall ♪
♪ If he up, watch him fall, ♪
♪ (censored) I can't (censored) y'all ♪
♪ If I wasn't rappin' baby, I
would still be ridin' Mercedes ♪
♪ Chromin' shinin' sippin' daily, ♪
♪ No rest until whitey pay me ♪
♪ Now what y'all know
'bout them Texas boys ♪
♪ Comin' down in candied toys, ♪
♪ Smokin' weed and talkin' noise ♪
- [Jay-Z] ♪ We be big
pimpin' spendin' cheese ♪
♪ We be big pimpin', on B.L.A.D.'s ♪
♪ We be big pimpin', down in P.A.T. ♪
♪ It's just that Jigga Man,
Pimp C, and B-you-N B ♪
♪ 'Cause we be big
pimpin, spendin' cheese ♪
♪ And we be big pimpin', on B.L.A.D.'s ♪
♪ 'Cause we be big pimpin' in P.A.T. ♪
♪ It's just that Jigga Man,
Pimp C, and B-you-N B ♪
♪ On the canopy, my stamina be ♪
♪ Enough for Pamela Anderson Lee ♪
♪ (censored) ♪
♪ Made my too long for gamblin' me ♪
♪ But still sitting on blades ♪
♪ Sipping that ray ♪
♪ Sittin' on the corner
of my block hustling ♪
♪ Getting off (censored) ♪
♪ Double what I paid ♪
♪ Getting it right through customs ♪
♪ It'll sell by night ♪
♪ Its egg shell white ♪
♪ I got so many (censored) ♪
♪ If the man find out ♪
♪ It will land me in jail for life ♪
♪ But I'm still big
pimpin', spending cheese ♪
♪ With Bun B, Pimp C, and Timothy ♪
♪ We got chicks in the back of the truck ♪
♪ Laughing it up ♪
♪ Jigga Man: That's what's up ♪
♪ We be big pimpin', spending cheese ♪
♪ We be big pimpin', on B.L.A.D.'s ♪
♪ We be big pimpin', down in P.A.T. ♪
♪ It's just that Jigga Man,
Pimp C, and B-you-N B ♪
♪ We be big pimpin', spending cheese ♪
♪ We be big pimpin', on B.L.A.D.'s ♪
♪ We be big pimpin', down in P.A.T. ♪
♪ It's just that Jigga Man,
Pimp C, and B-you-N B ♪
(music fades)